{
    "subject": "resource/Hardcore_(2015_film)",
    "predicate": "property/producer",
    "object": "resource/Timur_Bekmambetov",
    "human_readable": "Timur Bekmambetov produced the film 'Hardcore'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.966780424118042,
            "question": "Besides 'Hardcore', what other films has Timur Bekmambetov produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9100407361984253,
            "question": "What is the name of the film produced by Timur Bekmambetov?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8848365545272827,
            "question": "Timur Bekmambetov is known for producing what kind of films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8716959357261658,
            "question": "Has Timur Bekmambetov won any awards for his work on 'Hardcore'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7884180545806885,
            "question": "Who produced the film 'Hardcore'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.738532304763794,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Timur Bekmambetov."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6880636811256409,
            "question": "Are there any other notable films by Timur Bekmambetov?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5255616903305054,
            "question": "What is the plot of the film 'Hardcore'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4012903869152069,
            "question": "How was the film 'Hardcore' received by critics and audiences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38424909114837646,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Hardcore' likely to belong to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Timur Bekmambetov produced the film 'Hardcore'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1103_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How was the film 'Hardcore' received by critics and audiences?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1103_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of the film 'Hardcore'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1103_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other notable films by Timur Bekmambetov?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1103_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1103_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1103_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1103_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1103_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1103_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1103_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1103_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1103_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1103_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1103_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Yes.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": "**Rewrite**: Director Ilya Naishuller's film \"Hardcore\" was brought to life by producer Timur Bekmambetov."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " Yes, Timur Bekmambetov produced the film 'Hardcore'. The information provided suggests that a premiere for this film was held on March 30, 2016, in Moscow, Russia, and Timur Bekmambetov is associated with its production."
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The name of the producer given is Timur Bekmambetov but one of the photos shows a person named Sergei Yakhontov, who is identified as a producer, and there's no information that contradicts this.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}